[{"question":" When you create a new, blank presentation, you begin with one blank slide. What is the layout name of this slide?","options":[{"text":"Blank","correct":false},{"text":"Title slide","correct":true},{"text":"Title and Content","correct":false},{"text":"Title Onty","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What do you use to align objects on a slide to one another?","options":[{"text":"Layout tools","correct":false},{"text":"Arrange tools","correct":true},{"text":"Design Ideas feature","correct":false},{"text":"Picture tools","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which option must be enabled if you want to manipulate the playback of a video file during a presentation?","options":[{"text":"Record Side Show","correct":false},{"text":"Use Presenter View","correct":false},{"text":"Show Playback Controls","correct":false},{"text":"Show Media Controls","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which feature analyzes the content of your slides and offers suggested options?","options":[{"text":"Design ideas","correct":true},{"text":"Smartart","correct":false},{"text":"Browse for Themes","correct":false},{"text":"Add-Ins","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Where can you configure advanced PDF options?","options":[{"text":"the Options tab","correct":false},{"text":"the Home tab","correct":false},{"text":"the Print dialog box","correct":true},{"text":"the Share tab","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which tab is best for adding various types of objects to slides?","options":[{"text":"Animations","correct":false},{"text":"view","correct":false},{"text":"File","correct":false},{"text":"Insert","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which SmartArt category can you use to make informational graphics out of bullet points?","options":[{"text":"all of these answers","correct":true},{"text":"Pyramid","correct":false},{"text":"List","correct":false},{"text":"Matrix","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is NOT checked when you run the Accessibility Checker?","options":[{"text":"reading order","correct":false},{"text":"slide titles","correct":false},{"text":"missing alt text","correct":false},{"text":"grammar","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" How can you change the appearance of a table in one click?","options":[{"text":"Apply a cell stye.","correct":false},{"text":"Apply a graphic style.","correct":false},{"text":"Apply a table style.","correct":true},{"text":"Right-click a table and choose a new style.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which option changes a text box so that it automatically changes shape to fit longer text?","options":[{"text":"Resize shape to fit text","correct":true},{"text":"Do not autofit","correct":false},{"text":"none of these answers","correct":false},{"text":"Shrink text on overflow","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which three shadow properties can be adjusted in PowerPoint?","options":[{"text":"A, B, C","correct":false},{"text":"A, C, E","correct":false},{"text":"B, C, D","correct":false},{"text":"C, D, E","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```\nA. Focal Point\nB. Depth\nC. Blur\nD. Angle\nE. Distance\n```"},{"question":". You want your presentation to play continuously on screen, What option must you set?","options":[{"text":"Use Presenter view","correct":false},{"text":"Advance slides manually","correct":false},{"text":"Advance slides automatically","correct":false},{"text":"Loop continuously until 'Esc'","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement about the Compress Pictures command is true?","options":[{"text":"You can compress all images at the same time.","correct":true},{"text":"You cannot delete cropped areas.","correct":false},{"text":"There are no options for print output.","correct":false},{"text":"You can compress only one image at a time.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You have a Word document you would like to import as an outline into a PowerPoint presentation. How should you format the text in your Word document that you want to be the slide content?","options":[{"text":"Heading Style 2","correct":true},{"text":"Subtitle","correct":false},{"text":"Content Style","correct":false},{"text":"List 2","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nHighlight the content you want to use as a slide title, and select Heading 1 in Styles.\nHighlight the content you want to use as the slide text, and select Heading 2 in Styles.\nIf your Word document contains no Heading 1 or Heading 2 styles, PowerPoint will create a slide for each paragraph in your content.\n```"},{"question":". In what manner can you filter comments?","options":[{"text":"by length","correct":false},{"text":"by author","correct":true},{"text":"by date","correct":false},{"text":"by urgency","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which Arrow Options choice will hide the mouse cursor when presenting, except when the cursor is moved?","options":[{"text":"Automatic","correct":true},{"text":"Hidden","correct":false},{"text":"none of these answers","correct":false},{"text":"Visible","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nIf hidden is selected the courser stays hidden no matter what.\n```"},{"question":". Which chart type is best suited for displaying annual financial data for a 10-year period?","options":[{"text":"donut chart","correct":false},{"text":"line or area chart","correct":true},{"text":"area chart","correct":false},{"text":"pie chart","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". If you want to create an organizational chart, which SmartArt category works best?","options":[{"text":"Pyramid","correct":false},{"text":"Relationship","correct":false},{"text":"Hierarchy","correct":true},{"text":"Matrix","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". When printing multiple handouts, which option will group multipage documents together and make them easier to distribute?","options":[{"text":"Print on Both Sides","correct":false},{"text":"Uncollated","correct":false},{"text":"Print One-sided","correct":false},{"text":"Collated","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How can you adjust which data in a table is used when working on a chart?","options":[{"text":"Click the Switch Row/Column button.","correct":false},{"text":"Click the Refresh Data button.","correct":false},{"text":"Click the Select Data button.","correct":true},{"text":"Click the Edit Data button.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which view lets you see additional information on a second monitor when delivering a presentation?","options":[{"text":"Normal view","correct":false},{"text":"Reading view","correct":false},{"text":"Slide Sorter view","correct":false},{"text":"Presenter view","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". A picture looks good in your slide show but pixelated when you print it. How can you fix this?","options":[{"text":"Compress the picture and use the Print (220 ppi) resolution setting.","correct":false},{"text":"Select Best scale for slide show, increase the picture resolution and resize the picture to the original size","correct":false},{"text":"Remove picture compression.","correct":true},{"text":"Change the printer property settings to print in a higher resolution.","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```Personal Hint:\nFile Tab -> Options -> Advanced -> Image Size and Quality -> Do not compress images in file\nFile Tab -> Options -> Advanced -> Print -> High quality\n```"},{"question":". You have inserted a video on a slide and want the video to automaaticlly start 2 seconods after the associated slide appears. How can you accomplish this?","options":[{"text":"Use playback timings.","correct":false},{"text":"Use animation timings.","correct":true},{"text":"Use animation triggers.","correct":false},{"text":"Use video timings.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". When inserting pictures, how can you avoid distorting the pictureif it is resized later?","options":[{"text":"Use best scale for slide show.","correct":false},{"text":"Lock the aspect ratio.","correct":true},{"text":"Compress the picture.","correct":false},{"text":"Set the picture to be relative to the orignal picture size.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which Protect Presentation option protects a presentation from accidental changes?","options":[{"text":"Always Open Read-Only","correct":true},{"text":"Add a Digital Signature","correct":false},{"text":"Encrypt with Password","correct":false},{"text":"Mark as Final","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How can you change colors in your presentation all at once without changing the design?","options":[{"text":"Apply a Color Template.","correct":false},{"text":"Apply a Color Theme.","correct":true},{"text":"Apply a Color Palette.","correct":false},{"text":"Customize the Color Fills.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What function allows you to borrow slides from a presentation fro an other presentation?","options":[{"text":"Borrow Slides","correct":false},{"text":"There is no special fuction. You must use Copy and Pase","correct":false},{"text":"Reuse Slides","correct":true},{"text":"Find Slides","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the term used for the arrangement of elements on a slide, such as Title and Content?","options":[{"text":"theme","correct":false},{"text":"design","correct":false},{"text":"sheme","correct":false},{"text":"layout","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How would you change a list of text to a visual diagram on a slide?","options":[{"text":"Convert to WordArt.","correct":false},{"text":"Convert to Shapes.","correct":false},{"text":"Convert to SmartArt.","correct":true},{"text":"Convert to Picture.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You need to reorder the levels of shapes on a SmartArt diagram. How can this be done","options":[{"text":"Retype the text","correct":false},{"text":"Change the shapes from rifht to left.","correct":false},{"text":"Promote Shapes and/or Demote Shapes.","correct":true},{"text":"Move the shapes up and down.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Why would you trim a video?","options":[{"text":"To crop the video thumbnail.","correct":false},{"text":"To resize the video.","correct":false},{"text":"To remove background noise in the video.","correct":false},{"text":"To remove some of the beginning and/or end of the video.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How would you save your layouts, colors, fonts, effects, background styles and content for others to use with their presentations?","options":[{"text":"Export the file as a template.","correct":true},{"text":"Save the file as a PDF.","correct":false},{"text":"Save the file as a POTX.","correct":false},{"text":"Save the file as a PPTX.","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nPersonal Hint: There are multiple file suffixes for templates (.potx, .potm, .pot).\n```"},{"question":". You are creating an industrial presentation of a new software program and would like to include an image of your program. How can you use PowerPoint to do this?","options":[{"text":"Use the Copy command.","correct":false},{"text":"Use the Screenshot command. (Office2019)","correct":true},{"text":"Use the Print key.","correct":false},{"text":"Use the Capture Screen command.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How can you add more layouts to the Layout Gallery?","options":[{"text":"Customize the Layout Gallery.","correct":false},{"text":"Add Slide Layouts to the Slide Master.","correct":true},{"text":"Use the Add Layouts command.","correct":false},{"text":"Use the Insert Layouts command.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Why would you use the Outline view?","options":[{"text":"To see only the text in placeholders.","correct":true},{"text":"To present the slides at a high level.","correct":false},{"text":"To add text from a Word document.","correct":false},{"text":"To organize your slides.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The text on the left and right of the slide are cut off in print preview. How can you fix this in the printer settings?","options":[{"text":"Unselect High Quality.","correct":false},{"text":"Select Scale to Fit Paper.","correct":true},{"text":"Select Frame Slides.","correct":false},{"text":"Select Frame Slides.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In addition to organizing your slides, how else can sections increase your productivity?","options":[{"text":"In addition to organizing your slides, how else can sections increase your productivity?.","correct":false},{"text":"All the slides in a section can be selected at once to apply changes such as transitions, layouts or hiding slides.","correct":true},{"text":"Sections can be exported as a separate presentation.","correct":false},{"text":"You can resize all the slides in a section at once.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You have many slides that you need to reorder. How would you accomplish this?","options":[{"text":"Move the slides in Slide Show view.","correct":false},{"text":"Renumber the slides in Outline view.","correct":false},{"text":"Move the slides in the Slide Sorter view.","correct":true},{"text":"Reset the slide footers.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What can be seen in Presenter view?","options":[{"text":"Timer.","correct":false},{"text":"Notes.","correct":false},{"text":"Side Navigator.","correct":false},{"text":"all of these answers.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How can you format the entire contents of a text box?","options":[{"text":"Click the dashed/dotted border of the text box.","correct":false},{"text":"Right-click the text box and select Select All.","correct":false},{"text":"Click the Fond button on the Home tab.","correct":false},{"text":"Double-click any word in the text box.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You have a large number of objects on your slide. How can you use the selection pane to help you identify the objects quickly?","options":[{"text":"Select the show/hide icons next to the objects.","correct":false},{"text":"Rename the objects with meaningful names.","correct":true},{"text":"Drag and drop the objects.","correct":false},{"text":"Tab through the objects and note each object as it's highlighted.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How would you ensure a consistent appearance and placement across your slides even though the content might be different?","options":[{"text":"Use fonts.","correct":true},{"text":"Use styles.","correct":false},{"text":"Use bullet points.","correct":false},{"text":"Use layouts.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How can you add icons to SmartArt?","options":[{"text":"Select the picture icon in a SmartArt Picture Diagram.","correct":false},{"text":"Select the icon in a SmartArt Icon Diagram.","correct":false},{"text":"Select Insert Icon and place it on top of the SmartArt Diagram.","correct":false},{"text":"Select a SmartArt shape and select Insert Icon.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""}]